Finding aid to the Classes of 1921-1930 records CA.MS.01019
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1927 records, 1923-2002; 10.896 linear feet (24 containers)
  - Barnes, Marjorie Clark (class notes) (Box 1990.1)
  - Brown, Mabel S. (scrapbooks) (Box 1991.2)
  - Doran, Mary (photograph), 1927; 1 items (1 photograph) (Box 1988)
  - Hamburger, Elizabeth (scrapbooks) (Box 1991.1)
  - Hamburger, Elizabeth (photograph), 1927; 1 items (1 photograph) (Box 1991.1)
  - Haner, Frances G. (photograph), 1927; 1 items (1 photograph) (Box 1988.1)
  - Hubbell, Marion (correspondence) (Box 1992)
  - Faterson, Jean (post grad) (Box 1993)
  - Maurer, Carol (Admission card, photographs, Smith College Monthly membership invitation), approximately 1923-1950; 1 folders (1 folder in a box of miscellaneous CA accessions) (Box Shared)
  - Miner, Frances M. (photograph), 1927; 1 items (1 photograph) (Box 1989)
  - Mitchell, Harriet G. (photo album) (Box 1993.2)
  - Roe, Anne Brokaw (Box 1993.1)
  - Sharon, Anna Marcella (memorabilia book) (Box 1994.1)
  - Shea, Eleanor (scrapbook) (Box 1994.1)
  - Shea, Eleanor (65th reunion photo album) (Box 1994.2)
  - Tebbetts, Dorothy (correspondence) (Box 1994)
- Class of 1928 records, 1923-1993; 16.5 linear feet (26 containers)
  The Class of 1928 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1928, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1928 was the fiftieth graduating class of Smith College.
  - Commencement, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1924 (Box 1995, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1924-1925 (Box 1995, Folder 6)
  - General, undated (Box 1995, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1924-1928; 1977 (Box 1995, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Day, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 12)
  - Class Letters, 1928-1987 (Box 1995, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1929 (Box 1996, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 1996, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1938-1943 (Box 1996, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1996, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 1996, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1996, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 1996, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 1996, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 1996, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Box 1996, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1993 (Box 1996, Folder 11)
  - Reunion Costume (Box 1996.1)
  - Class Secretary's Records, 1955-1983 (Box 1995, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbook-A-F (Box 1996.2)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbook-G-L (Box 1996.3)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbook-M-Q (Box 1996.4)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbook-R-Z (Box 1996.5)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 16)
  - Songs, 1924-1928 (Box 1995, Folder 17)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1926 (Box 1995, Folder 18)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1926 (Box 1995, Folder 19)
  - Step Sings, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 20)
  - Class Supper, 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 21)
  - Individuals A-K (Box 1997)
  - Individuals L-Z (Box 1998)
  - Brown, Margaret Levering (photo album) (Box 2010.2)
  - Bullard, Polly Ethel (correspondence) (Box 1999)
  - Chittim, Margaret Lee (memorabillia book) (Box 2010.2)
  - Goodwin, Helen Warren (class notes, drawings) (Box 1999.1)
  - Hirschberg, Nell (Box 1999.2)
  - Kendrew, Lucy Eliza (correspondence) (Box 2000)
  - Morrow, Anne Spencer (publications and clippings) (Box 2001)
  - Otis, Elizabeth Gray (memorabilia book) (Box 2010.2)
  - Perry, Lois Newton (Correspondence), 1924-1926 (Box 2002)
  - Perry, Lois Newton (Correspondence, class notes, papers), 1927-1928 (Box 2003)
  - Perry, Lois Newton (Class notes, scrapbook) (Box 2004)
  - Rinaldo, Harriet Rachel (correspondence), 1925-1928 (Box 2005)
  - Rinaldo, Harriet Rachel (correspondence, SSW), 1928-1929 (Box 2006)
  - Salmon, Katharine Bush (correspondence and post grad) (Box 2007)
  - Salmon, Katharine Bush (Box 2008)
  - Stoffregen, Elizabeth (Box 2008.1)
  - Taylor, Sarah Wingate (post grad) (Box 2009, Box 2010)
  - Trull, Ellenor Thorndike (scrapbook and memorabilia) (Box 2010.1)
  - Trull, Ellenor Thorndike (scrapbook, memories of commencement, and reunion) (Box 2010.3)
  - White, Helen (scrapbook) (Box 2010.4)
- Class of 1929 records, 1925-1996; 16.208 linear feet (26 containers)
  The Class of 1929 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1929, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1929 was the fifty-first graduating class of Smith College.
  - Alumnae Leadership Council Reports, 1992 (Box 2011, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Class Officers), 1954-1964 (Box 2011, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (Class Officers), 1966-1969 (Box 2011, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Class Officers), 1975-1980; undated (Box 2011, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1925 (Box 2011, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1925-1926 (Box 2011, Folder 11)
  - Groups, 1925-1929 (Box 2011, Folder 12)
  - Class Historian, 1966-1974 (Box 2011, Folder 13)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 14)
  - Ivy Day, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 15)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 16)
  - Junior Prom, 1928 (Box 2011, Folder 17)
  - Last Chapel, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 18)
  - Class Letters-General, 1931-1969 (Box 2011, Folder 19)
  - Class Letters-General, 1970-1987; undated (Box 2011, Folder 20)
  - Class Letters-Alumnae Fund, 1930-1958 (Box 2011, Folder 21)
  - Class Letters-Alumnae Fund, 1959-1982; 1996; undated (Box 2011, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954; 1967; undated (Box 2011, Folder 23)
  - Officers, 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 24)
  - Reunions-General, undated (Box 2013, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 2013, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 2013, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 2013, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1944 (Box 2013, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 2013, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 2013, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 2013, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 2013, Folder 9)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, 1964 (Box 2013, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2013, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2013, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 2013, Folder 13)
  - Reunion, 1979 (Box 2014.1)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-A-Bixler, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 1)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Blanchard-Cohen, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 2)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Connolly-Dunne, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 3)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-East-Grinnan, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 4)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Gilmore-Herold, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 5)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Holden-Kiefer, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 6)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Kirkbride-Manson, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 7)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Martin-Pitts, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 8)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Polacheck-Rogers, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 9)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Rose-Smith, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 10)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Sohst-Thayer, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 11)
  - 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Tripp-Zerby, 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 2013, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2013, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2013, Folder 16)
  - Reunion Scrapbooks and Memorabilia (Box 2016.6)
  - Reunion scrapbook (Box 2016.7)
  - Class Secretary's Records-A-Be (Box 2015, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Bi-Ch (Box 2015, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Cl-E (Box 2015, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records-F-Go (Box 2015, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Gr-Hi (Box 2015, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Ho-J (Box 2015, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Records-K-L (Box 2015, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Records-M (Box 2016, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records-N-Ph (Box 2016, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Pi-Ri (Box 2016, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Ro-Sc (Box 2016, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Se-Sq (Box 2016, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Records-St-Z (Box 2016, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box 2016, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks A-C (Box 2016.1)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks D-H (Box 2016.2)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks J-P (Box 2016.3)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks R-S (Box 2016.4)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks T-Z (Box 2016.5)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1929 (Box 2012, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1929 (Box 2012, Folder 2)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1929 (Box 2012, Folder 3)
  - Songs, 1925-1929 (Box 2012, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1927 (Box 2012, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Push, 1927 (Box 2012, Folder 6)
  - Step Sings, 1929 (Box 2012, Folder 7)
  - Class Supper, 1929 (Box 2012, Folder 8)
  - Individuals A-J (Box 2017)
  - Individuals K-Sh (Box 2018)
  - Individuals Si-Z (Box 2019)
  - Butler, Mary Frances (photo album) (Box 2020.3)
  - Carrier, Constance Virginia, post grad (Box 2018.1)
  - Cohen, Gertrude (photograph album) (Box 2020.4)
  - Eaton, Alice Allen (correspondence) (Box 2019.2)
  - Haydock, Dorothea R. (scrapbook) (Box 2020.5)
  - Houghton, Ruth (honors thesis, The Silk Industry in Northampton) (Box 2020.6)
  - Thayer, Eleanor Wiley (memorabilia book) (Box 2020)
  - Young, Mary Louise (correspondence, course notes) (Box 2020.1)
  - Young, Mary Louise (course notes) (Box 2020.2)
- Class of 1930 records, 1926-2000; 8.917 linear feet (16 containers)
  The Class of 1930 was the fifty-second entering class and the fifty-second graduating class of Smith College.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  As a preservation measure, researchers must use digital copies of audiovisual materials in this collection. Please consult with Special Collections staff to request the creation of and access to digital copies.
  The Class of 1930 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1930, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  - Addresses, 1926-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 1)
  - Class Baby, 1931 (Box 2021, Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1928-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Music, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 8)
  - Fund Letters, undated (Box 2021, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1926-1927 (Box 2021, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1926 (Box 2021, Folder 11)
  - General, undated (Box 2021, Folder 12)
  - Groups, 1926-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 13)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 14)
  - Ivy Day, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 15)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 16)
  - Junior Prom, 1929 (Box 2021, Folder 17)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1929 (Box 2021, Folder 18)
  - Junior Ushers, 1929 (Box 2021, Folder 19)
  - Last Chapel, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 20)
  - Last Sing, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 21)
  - Class Letters, 1956-1967 (Box 2021, Folder 22)
  - Class Letters, 1970-2000 (Box 2021, Folder 23)
  - Reunions-General, undated (Box 2022, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1931 (Box 2022, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Reunion Register, 1931; 1935; 1940 (Box 2022, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 2022, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 2022, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 2022, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 2022, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Film, 1955, Susan C. Moynihan; Mackenzie, Helen, Class of 1930; 1 items (1 reel of 8mm film) (Box 2022, Folder 9)
    filmstrips; Susan C. Moynihan
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 12)
  - Reunions-Reunion Book, 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 2023, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 2023, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 2023, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 2023, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire: Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 2024, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire: Tabulations and Report, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 5)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 6)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 9)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy, 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 2023, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 2023, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2023, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 2023, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 2023, Folder 9)
  - Reunion- Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 2024.1)
  - Reunions-Songs, 1980; undated (Box 2023, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1985 (Box 2023, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1985 (Box 2023, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1990 (Box 2023, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1995 (Box 2023, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 2000 (Box 2023, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Reunion Napkin with Cartoon, undated (Box 2023, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2024.2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 24)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 25)
  - Senior Statistics, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 26)
  - Songs, 1926-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 27)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1928 (Box 2021, Folder 28)
  - Sophomore Push, 1928 (Box 2021, Folder 29)
  - Step Sing, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 30)
  - Class Supper, 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 31)
  - Individuals A-Cr (Box 2025)
  - Individuals Cu-Hi (Box 2025.1)
  - Individuals Ho-Z (Box 2026)
  - Bolton, Dorothea (memorabilia book) (Box 2026.3)
  - Dunning, Alma Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 2026.4)
  - Fowler, Virginia (Class notes) (Box 2026.1)
  - Fowler, Virginia (Class notes) (Box 2026.2)
  - Hockridge, Marion Lucille (correspondence, photo album, class papers) (Box 2027)
  - Palmer, Alice Hoyt (photograph album and memorabilia) (Box 2027.1)
  - Sayre, Margaret Culbreth (photo album, scrapbook) (Box 2027.2)